Joan McBreen papers
Emory University
- Writings by others, 1985-2002, Series 3; Boxes 19-20
  - McMarnus, Suzy, "In the Beginning," typescript (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - McNeilly, K., "Grackle," and "Deli," poem typescripts [See Correspondence (Series 1): April 2, 1991] (Box -, Folder -)
  - Meidar, Edie, "Ship of Mules," photocopied manuscript (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Mills, Lia, "I Won't Go Back to It: Irish Women Poets and the Iconic Feminine," essay typescript, 1994 [includes correspondence from McBreen] (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Mitchell, Jack, "Galway's Tajmichal," poem typescript, March 4, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Molloy, Edel, "each time I write," poem typescript, July 15, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Mongan, Tom, "Frosty Night in Carnaross," and other poems, typescripts and photocopies of manuscripts (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Morgan, William, "Efforts of an Apprentice practicing Verse in Innocence," poem collection typescript (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Na Freíye, Sainnatt, "Cause of the Trouble," play typescript [See Correspondence (Series 1): February 24, 1988] (Box -, Folder -)
  - Noonan, Martina, "Concrete and Slabs," poem manuscript (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - O'Beirn, Padriac, "Bite," and other poems, typescripts (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - O'Higgins, Una O'Malley, Twentieth Century Revisited, poetry collection typescript, February 9, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - O'Neill, Catherine, "Not Just a Woman," and other poems, typescripts (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Parkinson, Barbara, "Snakes Have Time for Me," and other poems typescripts, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Quart, Abigail, "The Spartan Boy," typescript (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Reidy, Gerard, "A fog forms in the valley," and other poems, typescripts, July 1991 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Sharkey, Aiden, "Curtains," and other poems, typescripts, September 1992 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - [?], Shelia, "The Necessary Angel," and other poems, typescripts, April 2005 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Simmons, James, "At the Frost Place," and "The First Nervous Irrevocable Steps," poem typescript, May 1993 [See Subject Files (Series 4): "Poet's House"] (Box -, Folder -)
  - Simmons, James, "If You Go to Enniskillen," poem typescript (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Snowdon, Peter, "At Stanton Harecourt (Hardly So)," typescript, September 17, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Tillinghast, Richard, "Wireless," and other poems, typescripts (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Unidentified writers, manuscripts and typescripts (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Vial, Noelle, "Accident of Time," and "Decision," poem typescripts, August 15, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Walsh, Kevin, "Minnesota," and other poems, typescripts (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Yeo, Peter, "Without You," and "An Imaginary Movie," poem typescripts, October 15, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 32)
- Subject files, circa 1980s-2003, Series 4; Boxes 21-25, BV1-3
  The series consists of subject files covering a variety of topics from circa 1980s to 2003, and document Joan McBreen's involvement in numerous literary endeavors such as the Galway Writer's Workshop, Listowel Writer's Week, and Yeats International Summer School. The series also consists of personal records, including address books, datebooks, and scrapbooks in which McBreen compiled clippings related to various topics of interest. McBreen also kept subject files on topics such as Irish politics and literary figures, including Eavan Boland, Seamus Heaney, Padraic Fallon, Ted Hughes, and George MacBeth. Finally, this series includes McBreen's files relating to her time as a student at the University College Dublin, such as correspondence and course material. Her dissertation can be found in Subseries 2.4: Other writings.
  - Address book, undated (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Address book, early 1980s (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - The Arts Council, Dublin, Ireland (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Awards, American Poetry Association, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Award, International Merit Award Winner, Atlanta Review, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Award, The Waterford Review, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Biographical sketches (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Boland, Eavan (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Brogan, Patricia; Burke (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Casey, Eamonn, Bishop of Galway [1 of 2] (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Casey, Eamonn, Bishop of Galway [2 of 2] (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Children's' writings (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Clifden Writer's Workshop (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Connaught Electronics (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Cork Women's Poetry Circle (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - The Cúirt International Festival of Literature, 1989-1999 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Dancing at Lughnasa (play) (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Datebook, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Datebook, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Datebook, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Fallon, Connor (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Fallon, Padraic, Celebration in Athenry, Ireland, June 1992 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - The Gallery Press (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Galway Writer's Workshop, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Galway Writer's Workshop, 1990s (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Heaney, Seamus (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - The History of Women Conference, Queen's University Belfast, May 1993 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Hughes, Ted (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - "Humours of Galway" Master Class, Galway, March 1992 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Invoices, 1988-2003 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Irish Writer's Union (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Kennedy, Anne [includes necklace] (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Listowel Writer's Week [1 of 2] (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Listowel Writer's Week [2 of 2] (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Macbeth, George (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Magdalene Laundries (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Na Gréine, Domhnall (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Notebook, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Notebook, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Poetry Ireland (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Poetry magazines, flyers and subscriptions (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Poets' House (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Poland trip, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - RTE (Radio Telefís Eíreann) (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Royalty statements, 1991, 1996-1997 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Salmon Publishing (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Scrapbook, November-December 1987 (Box BV1)
  - Scrapbook, 1990 [includes clippings regarding The Wind Beyond the Wall] (Box BV2)
  - Scrapbook, 1993 [includes clipping regarding the Magdalene homes] (Box BV3)
  - Story Line Press (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Tillinghast, Richard (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Tillinghast, Richard, Workshop, Cúirt International Festival of Literature, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - University College Dublin, Women's Studies Certificate, correspondence (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - University College Dublin, Women's Studies Certificate, course material [1 of 2] (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - University College Dublin, Women's Studies Certificate, course material [2 of 2] (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - University College Dublin, Women's Studies Certificate, course papers, 1992-1994 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - University College Dublin, Women's Studies Certificate, printed material (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - University College Dublin, Women's Studies Master's Degree, application materials (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Westport Writer's Workshop, April 1992 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - The White Page, book launch, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - The Wind Beyond the Wall, book launch, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Wynne-Jones, Nancy (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Yeats International Summer School, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Yeats International Summer School, 1990-1997 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Yeats, William Butler (Box 25, Folder 10)
- Printed material, 1985-2007, Series 5; Boxes 26-34; OP1-2
  This series is comprised of printed material by Joan McBreen, about Joan McBreen, and general printed items from 1985-2007. Although poems published between 1987 and 1999 make up the largest part of the printed material by McBreen, she did publish one letter to the editor of an unidentified newspaper concerning the value of modern poetry. In contrast to the narrow focus of the printed material by McBreen, the printed material about McBreen consists of a variety of published resources pertaining to the author, including articles, programs, announcements, promotional material, and reviews of many of her published poetry collections. Lastly, the general printed material, spanning from 1978-2007, is comprised of magazine articles, brochures, flyers, newsletters, newspaper clippings, poetry inserts, programs, travel materials, and numerous periodicals. Of note to researchers is McBreen's extensive collection of articles and clippings, which demonstrate an acute concern with the success of fellow Irish poets, Irish history, and with various papal scandals in Ireland.
  - Printed material by McBreen, Poems, 1986-1999
  - "Girl with Umbrella," and "The Wind Beyond the Wall," unidentified newspaper, undated (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - "The Green Quilt," unidentified newspaper, undated (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - "Silent Night," unidentified newspaper, undated (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - "A Song of Kilmovee," unidentified magazine, undated (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - "On Hearing My Daughter Play the Swan," unidentified journal, undated (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - "My Father," "There are Indians in Ireland," and "Classibawn," Tribune, December 5, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - "The Broken Swing," The Tuam Herald, 1987 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - "Another Woman," Outlet, 1987 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - "My Father," "The Peace-Keeper," and "Christmas in Tuam," Maryland Poetry Review, Spring/Summer 1987 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - "Classibawn," The Web: New Writing by Women, June 1987 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - "The Left Hand," Tribune, February 5, 1988 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - "The Caves," "River Music," and "The Saints," Tidings, Summer 1988 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - "Christmas," and "Winter Jasmine," The Herald, December 31, 1988 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - "Flying on the Back of a Seagull," Gown, Autumn/Winter 1989 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - "'Have you Checked the Woods for Indians?'," and "Letter to a Friend from an Adopted Town," The Great Tuam Annual, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - "Snow in September," stet, Spring 1990 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - "The Broken Swing," and "The Stones," Irish America, April 1990 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - "Postcards and a Photograph on my Bedroom Mirror," unidentified newspaper, November 19, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - "Letter to a Friend from an Adopted Town," City Tribune, January 25, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - "The Photograph of My Aunt," and "Eanach Cuain," Force 10, Autumn 1991 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - "Snow in September," "After Osip Mandelstam," and "This Light, This Silence," Maryland Poetry Review, Spring/Summer 1992 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - "Ben Bulben," Ms.chief, Summer 1992 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - "Inis Meain," flyer for "A Poetry Reading to Celebrate International Women's Day," March 7, 1993 [flyer is signed by other poets participating in reading] (Box OP2)
  - "The Mountain Ash," Windows, Summer 1993 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - "The Little Street," Althone Observer, August 12, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - "A Walled Garden in Moylough," and "Veronica," Westerly, Winter 1993 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - "Bog-Cotton," "Watches," The Clean Slice," "In the Brief Time Given," and "One for Sorrow," The Great Tuam Annual, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - "The Lost Brooch," "The Clean Slice, and "In the Brief Time Given," Tribune, March 18, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - "The Mountain Ash," Tuam Herald, October 1, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - "In the Brief Time Given," Tuam Herald, October 6, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - "Girl," unidentified newspaper, January 16, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - "Only when the two rise," Ropes, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Letter to the editors
  - "Modern Poetry," unidentified newspaper, February 18, 1988 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Printed material about McBreen, 1987-2004
  - General: Articles, 1988-2002 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - General: Programs and Announcements, 1987-2003 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - General: Promotional Material, 1990-2004 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Reviews: The Wind Beyond the Wall (1990), June 1990-September 1991 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Reviews: A Walled Garden in Moylough (1995), April-October 1995 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Reviews: The White Page (1999), December 1999 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Reviews: Winter in the Eye: New and Selected Poems (2003), May 2003 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Reviews: The Long Light on the Land (2004), November 2004 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - General printed material, 1985-2007
  - Articles, undated (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Articles, 1985-2005 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Brochures, undated and 1988-1993 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Brochures, 1994-2000 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Flyers, undated and 1987-2006 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Newsletters, 1988-1999 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Newspaper clippings, undated (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1983-1986 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1987-1989 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper clippings, February 1990-May 1991 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper clippings, June 1991-December 1992 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1993-1994 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1995 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1996-1997 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1998-1999 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2000-2005 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2006-2007 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Other printed material, 1990-1997 [includes business cards, various organization's calendars, fact sheets and notes, invite and press lists, and calls for papers] (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Poetry, inserts and photocopies, undated and 1988-2005 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Postcards, blank, undated (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Posters, 1991-2000 (Box OP1)
  - Press releases and catalogues, undated and 1989-1995 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Programs, undated [1 of 2] (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Programs, undated [2 of 2] (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Programs, 1978-1985 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Programs, 1986-1987 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Programs, 1988-1989 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Programs, 1990 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Programs, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Programs, 1992-June 1993 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Programs, July 1993-1994 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Programs, 1995-1996 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Programs, 1997 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Programs, 1998-2000 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Travel material, undated (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Travel material, 1989-1991 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Travel material, 1992-1995 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Travel material, 1996-1999 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - General printed material: periodicals
  - Carn: A Link Between the Celtic Nations, Number 10, Winter 1997-1998 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Clochadóir, undated (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Cois Coirbe, 1994 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - The Corran Herald, Number 28, 1995; Number 36, 2003-04 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Lines and Rhymes, Volume 1, undated (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Maryland Poetry Review, Volume 1, Number 1, 1986; Volume 2, Number 2, Fall 1987 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Ms. Chief, Number 4, 1993; Number 8, 1994 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Over the Bridge: The Bilingual Journal from Ireland, Summer 1987 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - P.N. Review, Volume 28, Number 2, November-December, 2001 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - The Ratpit: Donegal Literary Magazine, Number 2, August 1984 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Review of Postgraduate Studies: ROPES, Number 4, Spring 1995-96; Number 5, 1997; Number 6, 1998 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Tiger's Eye: Regional Craft Workshops, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Westerly, Number 1, March 1991 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Womanspirit: The Irish Journal of Feminist Spirituality, Volume 5, Number 2, October 1991 (Box 34, Folder 4)
- Photographs, 1979-2000, Series 6; Boxes 35-36
  This series consists of three categories of photographs, taken from 1979-2000: photos of Joan McBreen, photos of others, and photos of individual contributors to The White Page. Photographs of McBreen include portraits, publicity photos, and snapshots with literary colleagues, family, and friends. Photographs of others include many photos of McBreen's husband, children, and extended family, as well as various colleagues and poetry workshop participants. Lastly, photographs of The White Page contributors consist of publicity photos, portraits, and personal snapshots donated to McBreen for their use in the anthology on Irish women's poetry.
  Photographs of McBreen are arranged in chronological order; photographs of individual contributors to The White Page and other people and places are arranged in alphabetical order.
  - Joan McBreen
  - McBreen, Joan, portraits, undated (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - McBreen, Joan, portrait, Tuam Herald photo, undated [photographer, Ray Ryan] (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - McBreen, Joan, publicity photo, undated (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - McBreen, Joan, and unidentified individual, undated (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - McBreen, Joan, and unidentified man and woman, undated (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - McBreen, Joan, with coffee cup, publicity photos, undated (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - McBreen, Joan, portrait, circa late 1980s [photographer, Michael Connaughton] (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - McBreen, Joan, publicity photo, circa late 1980s (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - McBreen, Joan, and Joe McBreen, unidentified event, February 19, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - McBreen, Joan, portrait, June 1989 [photographer, Gerard Quinn] (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - McBreen, Joan, and W. Kotas, and unidentified individuals, Sligo, Ireland, November 30, 1989 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - McBreen, Joan, Mary O'Malley, and unidentified others, at Cúirt International Festival of Literature [circa 1980s-1990s] (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - McBreen, Joan, and family, portrait, circa late 1980s-early 1990s (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - McBreen, Joan, Kevin Brennan, and unidentified others [circa late 1980s-1990] (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - McBreen, Joan, Medbh McGuckian, Joe McBreen, and others at unidentified dinner [circa early 1990s] (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - McBreen, Joan, and daughter, unidentified speaking engagement, circa 1990s (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - McBreen, Joan, and family, graduation celebration, circa 1990s (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - McBreen, Joan, and unidentified individual, circa 1990s (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - McBreen, Joan, and unidentified individuals, Lissadell House, circa 1990s (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - McBreen, Joan, family and friends, family wedding, circa 1990s (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - McBreen, Joan, Jessie Lendennie, and Anne Kennedy, unidentified locations, circa 1990s (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - McBreen, Joan, Medbh McGuckian, and unidentified individuals, McGuckian's house, circa 1990s (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - McBreen, Joan, publicity photo, circa 1990s [photographer, Michael Connaughton] (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - McBreen, Joan, publicity photos, circa 1990s (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - McBreen, Joan, publicity photo shoot, 1990 [photographer, Brendan Lawlor] (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - McBreen, Joan, snapshot, 1990 (Box 35, Folder 26)
  - McBreen, Joan, and unidentified others, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 27)
  - McBreen, Joan, and unidentified others, poet's house, 1992 (Box 35, Folder 28)
  - McBreen Joan, and Penny Perrick, Malina book launch, May 17, 1993 [photographer, Tadhg Keady, I.P.P.A., N.U.J.] (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - McBreen, Joan, publicity photo, circa 1990s [photographer, Ray Ryan] (Box 35, Folder 30)
  - McBreen, Joan, and unidentified literary launch, October 2, 1997 [photographer, Tom Kennedy] (Box 35, Folder 31)
  - McBreen, Joan, publicity photos, circa late 1990s [photographer, Anne Kennedy] (Box 35, Folder 32)
  - McBreen, Joan, and Máire Holmes, Jessie Lendennie, Colette Nic Aodha, Mary O'Malley, and unidentified individuals, The White Page book launch, circa 1999 (Box 35, Folder 33)
  - McBreen, Joan, and The White Page contributors, release party, circa 1999 (Box 35, Folder 34)
  - McBreen, Joan, and The White Page contributors, book launch, 1999 [includes correspondence from Joan Newmann] (Box 35, Folder 35)
  - Other people and places
  - "Applecarth," house, undated (Box 35, Folder 36)
  - Bardwell, Leland, August 2000 (Box 35, Folder 37)
  - Bourke, Eva, Ted Dieppe, and Rita Ann Higgins, Kenny's Gallery, Galway, circa late 1990s (Box 35, Folder 38)
  - Campbell, Siobhan and Jean Valentine, ocean view, October 15, 1999 (Box 35, Folder 39)
  - Coveney, Dick, and Ronnie Coveney, unidentified event, undated (Box 35, Folder 40)
  - Fitzmaurice, Gabriel, circa 1990s (Box 35, Folder 41)
  - Kennedy, Anne, and unidentified individual, circa 1980s (Box 35, Folder 42)
  - McBreen children and others, undated (Box 35, Folder 43)
  - McBreen family photos, unidentified individuals, circa 1990s (Box 35, Folder 44)
  - McBreen, Joe, and children, at storefront, undated (Box 35, Folder 45)
  - McBreen, Joe, and unidentified colleague, December 21, 1989 (Box 35, Folder 46)
  - McBreen, Joe, and unidentified individuals, circa late 1990s (Box 35, Folder 47)
  - Unidentified class of children, May 1979 (Box 35, Folder 48)
  - Unidentified individuals, unidentified event, undated (Box 35, Folder 49)
  - Unidentified pair of children, undated (Box 35, Folder 50)
  - Unidentified parents with two children, Dylan and Eoghan, portraits, 1992 (Box 35, Folder 51)
  - Workshop participants, Galway writers' workshop, Bridge Mills, Galway, April 26, 1997 (Box 35, Folder 52)
  - The White Page (1999)
  - Berkeley, Sara (Box 35, Folder 53)
  - Bleakney, Jean, May 20, 1999 (Box 35, Folder 54)
  - Boland, Eavan, February 25, 1999 (Box 35, Folder 55)
  - Bourke, Eva, February 25, 1999 (Box 35, Folder 56)
  - Brennan, Deidre, February 25, 1999 (Box 35, Folder 57)
  - Brennan, Lucy (Box 35, Folder 58)
  - Brett, Heather (Box 35, Folder 59)
  - Burke-Brogan, Patricia, February 25, 1999 (Box 35, Folder 60)
  - Byron, Catherine (Box 35, Folder 61)
  - Campbell, Siobhán, August 3, 1997 (Box 35, Folder 62)
  - Cannon, Moya (Box 35, Folder 63)
  - Carr, Ruth (Box 35, Folder 64)
  - Cimino, Glenda (Box 35, Folder 65)
  - Cluysenaar, Anne, Spring 1996 (Box 35, Folder 66)
  - Connolly, Susan, November 15, 1998 (Box 35, Folder 67)
  - Cowman, Roz (Box 35, Folder 68)
  - Crowley, Vicki, February 25, 1999 (Box 35, Folder 69)
  - Cullen, Yvonne (Box 35, Folder 70)
  - Dáibhís, Bríd, February 25, 1999 (Box 35, Folder 71)
  - de Fréine, Celia (Box 35, Folder 72)
  - Donaldson, Moyra (Box 35, Folder 73)
  - Dorcey, Mary (Box 35, Folder 74)
  - Dowdican, Anna Marie (Box 35, Folder 75)
  - Duffy, Katherine, February 25, 1999 (Box 35, Folder 76)
  - Evans, Martina, February 22, 1999 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Fayne, Pauline, March 4, 1999 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Fitzpatrick-Simmons, Janice, June 25, 1999 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Fyfe, Anne-Marie (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Gamble, Isobel (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Gatley, Sarah, August 13, 1999 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Greene, Angela (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Greene, Pamela (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Hardie, Kerry, March 4, 1999 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Hartigan, Anne Le Marquand, March 23, 1999 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Higgins, Rita Ann, February 25, 1999 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Holmes, Máire (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Hurson, Tess (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Kelly, Maeve, May 13, 1999 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Kelly, Rita, March 4, 1999 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Kennedy, Ann (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Lendennie, Jessie, January 9, 1999 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - MacCarthy, Catherine Phil, February 26, 1999 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - MacGarrigle, Carmen, March 10, 1999 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Martin, Eilish (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - McCracken, Kathleen, March 23, 1999 (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - McDermott, Linda, April 1999 (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - Mc Kiernan, Ethna (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - McSkeane, Liz (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - Medbh, Máighréad, February 26, 1999 (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - Miller, Áine, February 26, 1999 (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - Moran, Linda, February 25, 1999 (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - Morrissey, Sinéad, March 23, 1999 (Box 36, Folder 28)
  - Murdoch, Iris (Box 36, Folder 29)
  - Newmann, Joan (Box 36, Folder 30)
  - Nic Aodha, Colette, February 24, 1999 (Box 36, Folder 31)